I mean, like Rush Limbaugh's
couch cushions after Shark Week.
I love Frozen.
I loved her. I loved her
like an ocean loves water.
An ocean is water.
More importantly, I liked her.
I really liked her, you know?
George Michael was right.
I'm never gonna dance again.
Fuck!
He's dead, too.
At least we still have Bowie.
Oh, Mr. Pool. David Bowie is...
Uh, uh, uh...
still with us.
We do. We'll always have Bowie.
I'm sorry.
Shot after shot,
it's not gonna change the
fact that I think you're...
Are you pissing? Are you
urinating right now?
You're making the face that
you make when you urinate.
Is he pissing? I'm on it!
There you go, Dopinder.
If you want to be a
contract killer...
you gotta handle a mop
before you handle a gun.
Although I don't
quite understand
how they are at all similar.
'Cause I could shove either
one up your ass and kill you.
Now, leave me.
I get it.
Go home, Wade.
I don't have a home, Weas, you know.
I got a...
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
You know what "fine"
stands for, Wade?
Fucked up, insecure,
needy, and emotional.
According to the...
Kubler-Ross.Yeah.
According to the
Kubler-Ross model...
denial is just one of the
five stages of grief.
Jesus Christ, Buck!
No more speaking lines for you.
Hey, bud. Bud.
Huh? THUG: Got a match?
Match?
Yes, I have one right here.
Don't make a move.
This is a stick-up.
What? THUG: You heard me.
Mister, Mister, put
down that gun.
Shut up. Now, come on.
Your money or your life?
Look, bud. I said, "Your
money or your life."
"I'm thinking it over!"
Motherfuck!
Fuck!
The hell you doin' here?
Don't you know how to knock?
I thought you saw me...
with your ears.
You're lucky I didn't
shoot you in the...
The wall?
The refrigerator? I'm
in so much pain.
I heard the news, sweetie.
I'm very sorry. I am.
What am I gonna do, Al?
Probably something terrible.
Knowing you.
It was my fault.
I fucking did this.
And all I wanna do is
grab her and see her
and tell her that I'm
sorry, and I can't.
She's gone.
Sweetheart, can you speak up?
It's a little hard to hear you
with that pity dick
in your mouth.
Now, look, sugar. You
need to just keep living.
Thank you...
Matthew McConaughey, your
words are a treasure.
Listen to the pain.
It's both history teacher
and fortune teller.
Pain teaches us
who we are, Wade.
Sometimes, it's so bad,
we feel like we're dying.
But we can't really live till
we've died a little, can we?
Wade?
Wade? I'm right here, Althea.
And that is the most
beautiful thing
I've ever heard.
And you're absolutely right.
I'm about to do
something terrible.
Precious, aren't they?
Whoa!
Are you a superhero?
Fucking A, sweetie.
What's your name?
Captain Delicious Pants.
Who's Captain Delicious Pants?
I can't believe
he's still alive.
I can't believe you left
the house in that shirt.
There's gotta be
some way to die.
I just need to die harder.
Trademark Fox.
Y'all caught up now?
Open for business.
Your crazy matches my crazy.
I will never, ever let
our child be named Todd.
Skee-Ball token.
You're a lot smarter
than I look.
About why we're
so good together.
I love you, Wade Wilson.
Ness?
Ness.
Ness, there's something here.
I can't get to you.
Your heart's not in
the right place.
Wait, hold on. What?
Your heart's not in
the right place.
Wait. What do you mean
my heart's not in the right place?
What does it...
I'm terribly sorry
for your loss, Wade.
You're broken.
Oh, God. I know that voice.
Well, Russell.
I hear you're handy
at picking locks.
There will be no
need for that here.
There's no locks on our doors,
no bars on our windows.
I know what you're thinking.
Why don't the kids just run?
Who would choose to
stay in such a place?
You stay because...
deep down inside, you know
you're unfit to leave.
Don't worry.
We can fix that.
Blessed are the wicked who
are healed by my hand.
"Heart's in the right place."
"Heart's in the right..."
What does that mean?
Take your mask off, Wade.
I wish you'd said "pants".
Let's play a game.
It's called "Adrien
Brody or Adam Brody?".
Now, close your eyes
and open your mouth.
You don't need to be funny here.
We must talk.
You need fresh start.
Such a glare.
It's like I'm on
stage at the Gaiety.
With training, you can be X-Man.
You're wasting your
time, Shiny Jesus.
I'm not X-Man material.
Understatement of the year.
Wade, Yukio.
Yukio, Wade.
What in the fuck
knuckles is this?
She's my girlfriend,
you intolerant shit.
Whoa! Pump the hate
brakes, Fox & Friends.
I'm just surprised
anyone would date you.
Especially Pinkie Pie
from My Little Pony.
I like this guy.
Give him a chance.
It's great seeing you like this.
Yeah.
Bye, Wade!
Now, some ground rules
while under our roof.
"Rule number one. No killing..."
"anyone ever, no
matter how bad."
"Rule two. Label everything
in refrigerator."
Wade?
Don't try to chase me. Wade!
I'm not ready to
be touched again.
All these old guys on the wall.
Who lives here,
Calista Flockhart?
Those were already damaged
after they fell there!
What am I supposed to
do around here, anyway?
Sit in a share circle,
talk about my feelings?
And how would I do that exactly?
'Cause where the
fuck is everyone?
It's always just you
and Negasonic Teenage
Longest Name Ever...
Enough!
I said no touching!
What the fuck?
You'd think the studio
would throw us a bone.
One that doesn't end
up in my mouth.
The first movie made more money
than the guy who invented pants.
They can't just dust off
one of the famous X-Men?
How 'bout that putz with
the giant pigeon wings?
What do those do anyway, huh?
Carry him three
feet off the ground
to snatch up the
nearest muffin crumb?
No, no, no!
I am not X-Man material at all.
First off...
I'm not even a virgin.
Second and more...
I should have left you
in the self-pitying
mess I found you in.
But this is what friends do.
They show up!
Not when convenient or easy.
When hard, and you
always make it hard.
You are unwell.
I'm sticking my neck
out bringing you here.
Wait. One of the assholes
who killed Vanessa got away.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
I thought you were gonna
kiss me for a second there.
Please know I wouldn't be
able to stop you if you did.
Wade, whoever they are...
we track them down and
bring them to justice.
It was me.
I'm the asshole who got away.
I killed every last one
of them, except me.
Couldn't kill me.
We were gonna start a family.
We were, uh...
We were gonna be a family.
Wade...
Vanessa is gone. She's
not coming back.
This may not be
family you want...
but it's family you need.
You have a good heart.
It belongs here
where it can grow.
What did you say?
About my heart?
I think I'm in the right place.
I'mma tell you what
the big lie is.
Toilet paper.
What's so bad about
toilet paper?
Gets the job done.
Does it really get the job done?
All right. Say you wake
up tomorrow morning...
and, hypothetically, find
some fresh shit on your face.
Your cheek, maybe a
little bit in the beard.
What the hell? I'm about
to be fucking sick!
What do you do?
Do you go to a bathroom
and tear off a piece
of dry tissue...
and rub it around on
your beard a little bit
and then go on, get
on with your day?
Go to church, maybe
dinner and a movie,
like nothing happened?
Where is this coming from, man?
But something did happen.
Your face smells like shit.
Right?
So what you would do,
is you would get some soap,
you'd get some hot water...
and you would scrub
the fucking shit
out of your beard for
10 straight minutes.
You could not scrub it enough.
Are you trying to make
me feel disgusting?
I'm starting to feel...
Toilet paper is a
pretty fine appetizer.
But, then...
Huggies Natural Care wet wipes.